# KRIS HOROWITZ

## SENIOR GAME DESIGNER



(415) 269-2363



kris.horowitz@gmail.com



Los Angeles, CA



kris.life

## SKILLS

Unity

Spreadsheets!!

Precise Documentation

Figma, Adobe XD, Balsamiq

Copywriting

Photoshop

Japanese, French

Am a fun person

## **EDUCATION**

### | BA in Linguistics and Theater

University of California, Santa Barbara 2009 – 2013

#### || Minor in French

University of California, Santa Barbara 2009 – 2013

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a senior game designer with 6+ years experience in FTP mobile games. I bring passion, novelty and pizzazz to all my projects. "Passion? Everyone says 'passion." (That's you talking.) No, really, I've written mobile game fan fic. *Twice*. I lead teams with the belief that game making should be fun. Other things I like include writing, linguistics and renaissance faires. Let's chat! I'll tell you about my side project. And fan fic.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Senior Game Designer**

Dots, NYC | 2020 - 2022

Led an undisclosed project from pitch to prototype. I developed the concept, vision and all design documentation. Gained expertise in making mobile games from the ground up.

- Personally tapped to pitch new game concepts for the studio
- Excellent new game track record: lead designer on three original titles, creator of the first game to ship from Dots in the past 6 years

#### **Game Designer**

Dots, NYC | 2017 - 2020

Designed features and events for both live-ops titles and unreleased projects.

- Created the concept for a casual puzzle game releasing on Apple Arcade fall 2022
- Led a team of six from prototype to pre-production for the above game
- Wrote clean, precise design documents and UI flows

#### **Junior Game Designer**

Dots, NYC | 2015 - 2017

Designed levels for the wildly successful game *Two Dots*. Additionally, I conceived and implemented new puzzle mechanics.

- Primary content creator for Treasure Hunts, a weekly event that drove a significant percentage of revenue at the time.
- Selected to improve event revenue for the sequel title, *Dots & Co*, because of my performance on *Two Dots*.